Guide to the Transport Workers Union of America Records WAG.235
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Files of Matthew Guinan, 1935-1978.
  - Offaly Social and Athletic Club: Matthew Guinan Testimonial Dance, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Office of Impartial Chairman, Transit Industry, 1951-1955 (Box 52, Folder 7A)
  - Ohio CIO Council, 1958-1960 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Oklahoma: "Right to Work", 1967 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Organizing: Airlines, 1966-1967 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Organizing Committee: Bay Area Rapid Transit (BART), 1971-1972 (Box 52, Folder 10A)
  - Organizing Committee: Dues Committee, 1935-1936 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Organizing Committee for Non-Profit Agencies, 1967-1968 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Organizing Drives, 1956 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Organizing: General, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Organizing: Port Authority, 1966-1967 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - O'Sullivan, Father Richard, 1964 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - O'Sullivan, Father Richard: Benefit Dance Events, 1960-1962 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Pan American Airways Stock Clerks, 1958-1959 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Pan American Airways Strike, 1958-1959 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Passenger Service Improvement Corporation of Philadelphia, Undated (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Penn Central Carmen, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Penn Central Election, 1968-1969 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Penn Central Railroad, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Penn Central Railroad, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Penn Central Railroad: Staff Reports, Area 1, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Penn Central Railroad: Staff Reports, Area 2, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Penn Central Railroad: Staff Reports, Area 3, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Penn Central Railroad: Staff Reports, Area 4, 1968-1970 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Penn Central Railroad: Staff Reports, Area 5, 1968-1969 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - Penn Central Railroad: Staff Reports, Area 6, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - Penn Central Railroad: Staff Reports, Area 7, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - Penn Central Railroad: Staff Reports, Area 8, 1968-1969 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Penn Central Railroad: Staff Reports, Area 9, 1968-1969 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Penn Central Railroad: Staff Reports, Miscellaneous, 1968-1969 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvania State AFL-CIO, 1970-1971 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Pepper, Claude, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Philadelphia: Frankford El Scandal (Clippings), 1961 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Philadelphia: Public Employee Bargaining, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Philadelphia: Watchdog Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Political Action, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Political Contributions: U.S. Congress, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Port of New York Authority: Robert Moses, 1962-1965 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Powerhouse Dispute: Flyers, Press Releases, Clippings, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Powerhouse Dispute: Utility Workers vs. TWU, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - President's Advisory Committee on Labor-Management Policy, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - President's Commission on Registration and Voting Participation, 1960-1963 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 15A)
  - Press Releases, 1953-1955 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Press Releases, 1956-1958 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Press Releases, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Press Releases, 1961-1963 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Press Releases, 1964-1965 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Press Releases, 1966-1967 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Press Releases, 1968-1969 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Press Releases, 1970-1971 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Press Releases, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1956-1958 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1964-1965 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1966-1971 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Publicity: Television, 1956-1958 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - Publicity: Film (Tom Costigan), 1966-1967 (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - Publicity: Flyers, 1955-1960 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Publicity: Flyers, 1961-1971 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Publicity: Mitchell-McNeil Bill, 1958 (Box 54, Folder 2A)
  - Publicity: Paul Miner Associates, 1957-1959 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Publicity: Paul Miner Associates, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Publicity: Television and Radio, 1952-1970 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Public Service Collective Bargaining, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Puerto Rico, 1958 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Purchase of Rockaway Line (LIRR), 1951 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Quill, Michael J., 1956; 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Quill, Michael J.: Dedication of Plaque at Eugene Debs House, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Quill, Michael J.: Letter on Organizing Strategy, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Quill, Michael J.: Memos, Statements, Etc., 1954-1958 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Quill, Scholarship, 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Quill, Shirley Garry, 1957-1970 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Railroad Adjustment Board, 1955 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Railroad Division, 1955; 1959 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Railroad Division, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Railroad Division, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Railroad Division, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Railroad Division, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Railroad Division, 1964-1965 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Railroad Division, 1966-1967; 1975 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Railroad Division: Benefits, 1967-1968 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Railroad Division: Charters, 1955 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Railroad Division: Ferry Strike, 1955 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Railroad Division: Finances, 1955-1956 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Railroad Division: Group Insurance Plan, Undated (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Railroad Division: Information Bulletins, 1966-1967 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Railroad Division: International Representatives, 1956-1957 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Railroad Division: Legal Aid Program, 1955 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Railroad Division: Legislation, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Railroad Division: Local 273, 1953-1957 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Railroad Division: Long Island Railroad, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Railroad Division: Pennsylvania Railroad, 1955-1959 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Railroad Division: Pennsylvania Railroad Strike, 1954-1955 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Railroad Division: Pennsylvania Railroad Strike (Clippings), 1956-1958 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Railroad Division: Pennsylvania Railroad StrikeLayoffs, 1956 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Railroad Division: Pennsylvania Railroad Strike, 1960 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Railroad Division: Pennsylvania Railroad Strike (Clippings), 1960 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Railroad Division: Pennsylvania Railroad StrikePublicity, 1960 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Railroad Division: Pennsylvania Railroad StrikePublic Reaction, 1960 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Railroad Division: Pennsylvania Railroad's Discrimination Re: Passes, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Railroad Division: Publicity, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Railroad Division: Secretary-Treasurer's Meeting, 1956 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Railroad Division: System Brands, 1955 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Railroad Division: Presidents Council, 1958-1959 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Railroad Division: Presidents Council, 1965-1969 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Railroad Division: Presidents Council, 1962 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - Railroad Merger, 1962 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Railroad Merger, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Railroad Retirement Board, 1955 (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Receipts and Expenditures, 1936 (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - Reciprocal Agreement and Recognition of Transfer Cards, 1956-1969 (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - Referendum, 1956-1958 (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - Representation Election: New York City, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - Research Material, 1966-1967 (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - Resident Appeals Committee, 1959-1963 (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - Resolutions and Policy, 1964-1967 (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - Retirement System: New York City Employees, 1962-1963 (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - Rice, Msgr. Charles Owen, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Right to Work Laws, 1958 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Right-to-Work Laws, 1961-1965 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - "Right Wing and the Unions" (Typescript), Undated (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Roadley, C. Robert, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1969-1971 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Ronan, Dr. William, 1970-1974 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Roosevelt Monument Committee, 1970 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Rubber Workers: O'Sullivan Strike, 1957 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Rustin, Bayard, 1967-1971 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Ryan, John J., 1966 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Sacher, Harry: Obituaries, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - San Francisco: Public Employee Organizing and Joint Council, 1972-1976 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Santo, John, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Safety, 1957 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - St. Patrick's Day, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Schawinski, Joseph, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Seal and Dues Stamps, Undated (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Secretary-Treasurer's Conference, 1958 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Secretary-Treasurers: Notices, 1956-1958 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Secretary-Treasurers: Notices, 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Service Employees International Union: Local 32-BJ, Undated (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Shatzkin, Bernard, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Sheehan, Frank, 1966-1968 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Shimrack, Milo, 1963-1964 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Simpson, Fredric, 1963-1965 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Social Democrats, USA, 1974-1975 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - South American Trip, 1958 (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Southeastern Pennsylvania Transportation Authority (SEPTA): Formation of, 1963-1964 (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; Poor People's March on Washington, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - Special Cases, 1959 (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - Staff: International and Local, 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - Staff: International and Local, 1952-1959 (Box 56, Folder 33)
  - Staff: International and Local, 1963-1965 (Box 56, Folder 34)
  - Staff: International and Local, 1966-1969 (Box 56, Folder 35)
  - Staff Pension Plan (TWU), 1955-1958 (Box 56, Folder 36)
  - Staff: Vehicles, 1961-1963 (Box 56, Folder 37)
  - Steel Strike, 1959 (Box 56, Folder 38)
  - Strikes (TWU): National List, 1953-1955 (Box 56, Folder 39)
  - Taft-Hartley Communist Clause: Archive Brown Case, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 40)
  - Tate, James H.J., 1967-1968 (Box 56, Folder 41)
  - Taxi Drivers Organizing Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 56, Folder 42)
  - Teachers' Unions, 1966-1969 (Box 56, Folder 43)
  - Safety and Health Committee (CIO), 1953 (Box 56, Folder 44)
  - Telegrams, 1959-1963 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Telegrams, 1964-1965 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Telegrams, 1966-1969 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Telegrams, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Telegrams (Obituary), 1969 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Third Avenue Transit Corporation, 1956 (Box 57, Folder 5A)
  - Transit Authority, 1957-1958 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Transit Authority, 1960-1964 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Transit Authority: Health Benefit Trust, 1960-1962 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Transit Authority: Hourly Rated Workers, 1962 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Transit Authority: Joseph O'Grady, 1956-1958 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Transit Authority: Sick Leave, 1955-1956 (Box 57, Folder 10A)
  - Transit Authority: Special Accounting Investigation, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 10B)
  - Transit Legislation: National, 1962-1964 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Transit Pay: Keyserling Report, 1976 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Transit Planning-National and Regional, 1962-1965 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Transit Supervisors Organization (TSO), 1962-1968 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Transit: Tables and Memos (Program Planners, etc.), 1975 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Transit Worker Pay Levels: Programs Planners Inc. Report, 1978 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - TWU Express, 1959-1960 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - TWU Express, 1961-1967 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - TWU Express: Finances, etc., 1956-1958 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - TWU Express: Oversize Editions (I), 1952-1954, 1959, 1966 (Box MSOS005, Folder 2)
  - TWU Express: Oversize Editions (II), 1952-1954, 1959, 1966 (Box MSOS005, Folder 3)
  - Transportation Bond Issue (NYC), 1971-1973 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Transportation Programs, 1964-1969 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Transportation Vehicles, Inc., 1959 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Triboro Bridge and Tunnel Authority, 1952 (Box 57, Folder 22A)
  - Tri-Partite Committee to Review New York City Municipal Bargaining Procedures, 1966 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Twenty-Five Cent Fare, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Unemployment, 1958 (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Unemployment Conference, 1959 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Uniformed Sanitation Men's Association, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Union Label and Service Trades Council, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - Union Optical Plan, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Union Workers Survey, 1967 (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - United Automobile Workers, 1967-1970 (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - United Federation of College Teachers, 1966; 1971 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - United Federation of Teachers, 1962-1963 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - United Federation of Teachers (Shanker, Rustin, etc.), 1967-1971 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - United Housing Foundation, 1956-1958 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - United Nations, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - United Negro College Fund, 1959 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Committee for a Democratic Spain, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, 1956-1960 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, 1961-1964 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, 1965-1969 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, 1970-1975 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - U.S. Department of State, 1964-1969 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - U.S. Department of Transportation, 1973-1975 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Clippings, 1959-1965 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Strike, 1959 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - United Transit Association, 1961 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Unity House, 1956-1958 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Usery, William J. (Secretary of Labor), 1969-1971 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Van Riper, Ellis, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Various Clippings (Oversize, includes LIFE Magazine), 1940-1949, 1966 (Box MSOS005, Folder 1)
  - Voter Registration, 1964; 1968 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Wage and Price Freeze, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Wage Rates, 1956-1958 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Wage RatesNew York City, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Wagner Memorial Fund, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Wagner, Robert F., Mayor, 1957; 1960-1962 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Wagner, Robert F: Mayoral Campaign, 1961 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Waldman and Waldman, 1966-1969 (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - West Shore RR Ferry, 1954-1955 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - Wicks Grievance Bill, 1955 (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - Wiltwick School for Boys, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - Wirtz, Willard (Secretary of Labor), 1963 (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Workmen's Compensation Board, 1956-1965 (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - Workmen's Compensation Laws, 1971-1974 (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - Youth March for Integrated Schools, 1958-1959 (Box 58, Folder 34)
- Series III: Files of Other Officers and Staff, 1911-1990.
  - Subseries III:A: Files of Gustav Faber, 1944-1959
    - Amalgamated Bank, 1951 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Applications, 1952-1953 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Butler, Michael, 1951 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - CIO, 1952 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - CIO: Civil Rights, 1952-1953 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - CIO: Civil Rights Committee, 1953 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - CIO: Correspondence, 1953 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - CIO: Executive Board, 1953 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - CIO: National Office, 1951 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - CIO: National Office, 1951-1952 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - CIO News, 1947 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - CIO: Political Action Committee, 1951 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - CIO: Political Action Committee, 1952-1953 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - CIO: Safety and Health Committee, 1954 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - CIO: Secretary-Treasurer's Meetings, 1953 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - CIO Unions, 1951 (I) (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - CIO Unions, 1951 (II) (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - CIO Unions, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - CIO: Vice-Presidents' Meeting, 1953 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Contributions, 1950-1951 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Contributions, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Contributions, 1953 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Convention, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Convention, 1952 (I) (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Convention, 1952 (II) (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Convention: Appeal, Gerald O'Reilly, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Convention: Appeal, J. McCarthy, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Convention: Appeal, James Towey, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Convention: Appeal, Joseph Parco, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Convention: Appeal, Joseph Reilly, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Convention: Appeal, Maurice Forge, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Convention: Appeal, Patrick Devine, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Convention: Appeal, Patrick J. Reilly, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Convention: Appeal, Richard Trepz, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Convention: Appeal, Stanley Davis, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Convention: Appeal, William Higgins, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Convention: Committees, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Convention: Credentials committee, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - Convention: Delegates and Alternates, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - Convention: Delegate Kits, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 26)
    - Convention: Nomination Committee (Transcript), Undated (Box 60, Folder 27)
    - Convention: Reports, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 28)
    - Convention: Resolutions, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1954 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: CIO Affiliates, 1953 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Locals, 1951-1952 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Locals, 1953 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Quill, Michael J., 1952-1953 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Duchon, V. (Duke), 1952 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Dwyer, Louis, 1951-1952 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Election Materials, 1953 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Express: General, 1951 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Finances, 1950-1951 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Finances: Audit Reports, 1948-1950 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Finances: Audit Reports, 1951-1952 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Finances: Audit Reports, 1953-1954 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Financial Statements, 1952-1953 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Fisher, Richard, 1950 (Box 61, Folder 18a)
    - Greater New York CIO Council, 1944-1948 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Grogan, William, 1948-1953 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Insurance, 1949-1953 (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - International Executive Board: Financial Committee, 1952; 1953 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - International Executive Board: Resident Appeals Committee, 1951 (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - International Executive Board: Resident Appeals Committee, 1954-1956 (Box 61, Folder 23a)
    - International Transport Workers' Federation (ITF), 1951-1953 (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - ITF Publications, Journals, Newsletters, 1951 (I) (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - ITF Publications, Journals, Newsletters, 1951 (II) (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Israel: Histadrut, 1951 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Job Applications, 1951 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Job Classifications, 1957 (Box 62, Folder 4a)
    - Kaelin, Andrew, 1952-1954 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Ladies Auxiliary, 1949 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Local 100: General, 1949 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Local 100: General, 1950 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Local 100: General, 1951-1952 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Local 100: General, 1953 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Local 100: Resolutions, 1948 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Local 208 (Clayton, OH): Problems, 1952 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Locals: Form Letters, 1947-1949 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Los Angeles Organizing Campaign, 1951-1952 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - National Labor Relations Board (NLRB), 1951 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - NLRB, 1952 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - NLRB, 1953 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - NLRB: United Railroad Workers of America, CIO, 1954 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - National Reporter (labor newspaper), 1951-1952 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - New York City CIO council, 1949; 1953 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - New York State CIO Council, 1948 (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - New York State CIO Council, 1951-152 (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - New York State CIO Council, 1952 (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - New York State CIO Council, 1953 (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - O'Donnell and Schwartz, 1951-1954 (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - Office of the Financial Secretary (Gustav Faber, legal counsel), 1953 (Box 62, Folder 26)
    - Organizing, 1951-1952 (Box 62, Folder 27)
    - Organizing, 1953-1954 (Box 62, Folder 28)
    - New Building, 1952 (Box 62, Folder 29)
    - Pension Plans (TWU and other unions), 1950-1953 (Box 62, Folder 30)
    - Pensions, 1952 (Box 62, Folder 31)
    - Philip Murray Memorial Fund, 1953 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Police Organizing Drive, 1951-1952 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Political Action, 1948-1951 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Political Action, 1952 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Political Action, 1953 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Publicity, 1945-1951 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Publicity, 1952-1953 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Publicity, 1954 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Publicity, 1956 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Publicity, 1957-1958 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Publicity, 1959 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Puerto Rican Support Campaign (CIO), 1952 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Puerto Rico, 1951 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Quill, Michael J., 1949-1952 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Railroad Division: Correspondence, 1953 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Railroad Division: Financial Statements, 1953 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Referendum: Election of International Officers, 1948 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Requests for Literature, 1951 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Ryan, John J., 1950-1951 (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - Simpson, Fred, 1952 (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Spiegel, Aaron, 1949 (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Staff, 1948-1949; 1951-1953 (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - TWU Express, 1949; 1952-1953 (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - TWU Express: Faber columns, 1951-1953 (Box 63, Folder 24)
    - United Railroad Workers of America, 1951 (I) (Box 63, Folder 25)
    - United Railroad Workers of America, 1951 (II) (Box 63, Folder 26)
    - United Railroad Workers of America, 1952 (I) (Box 63a, Folder 1)
    - United Railroad Workers of America, 1952 (II) (Box 63a, Folder 2)
    - United Railroad Workers of America: Minutes: General Executive Board, 1953 (Box 63a, Folder 3)
    - United States Government Agencies, 1950-1952 (Box 63a, Folder 4)
    - Wage Stabilization Reports: Goldberg Rulings, 1951 (Box 63a, Folder 5)
  - Subseries III:B: Files of Maurice Forge, 1937-1978
    - Amalgamated Association of Street Car Employees of America, 1939-1945 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - American Labor Party, 1940; 1942-1943 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - American Labor Party, 1944 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - American Labor Party, 1945-1946 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - American Labor Party, Fordham: News and Views, 1945 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - American Labor Party, Queens County, 1944 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - American Labor Party: Sunnyside-Woodside Neighbor, 1945 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - CIO, 1940-1942 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - CIO, 1943-1944 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - CIO, 1945-1946 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1937-1946 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Greater New York CIO Council: Minutes, 1947-1978 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Labor-Management Wartime Campaign (New York City), 1943 (Box 64, Folder 13)